YAUHENIYA ZIALENKA

JR. FRONT-END DEVELOPER



EDUCATION

Family physician

Belarusian State Medical University

2013 - 2019

Front-end/JS Course

The Rolling Scopes School

June, 2022 - now

EXPERIENCE

Nurse, 2017-2018

Hospital, MInsk

Nurse

Oncology Center, Minsk

Doctor

Hospital, Minsk

Junior Front-end developer

freelance

Expertise

Html5, CSS3,

Scss,

Fetch

TypeScript

JavaScript

ECI::::

ESLint

Yarn, npm

HTTP,HTTPS

Webpack

FlexBox

Grid

Grid

git,

Github

React, React Hooks

react-router-dom, react-hook-form

REST API

FrontEnd intern

Eventizer StartUp September, 2022 - now

2017-2018

2018-2019

2019-2022

2022-now

Windows,

Responsive

Web design

MacOS

Figma

OOP

Jest

SPA

PROFILE

My name is Yauhenia.

I'm 27 years old. I devoted 9 years to medicine and decided to change the field of activity. Now I study Front-end at Rolling Scopes School courses and I have a year of development experience.

I easily assimilate information, learn quickly, can easily switch from one task to another, like to cope with non-standard situations. I'm stress resistant, calm and ready to action.

I'm looking for a job or internship in Front-end development. I'm interesting in reactive technologies, especially React. My forte is medicine, so I can be very usefull in projects connected with wellness and health. But also curious and open to different spheres.

LANGUAGES

Russian, English - B1, Polish(beginner)

PROJECTS

Rolling Scopes test projects Eventizer

https://rolling-scopes-school.github.io/evgueniazet-JSFE2022Q3/online-zoo/

https://evgueniazet.github.io/cssBayan/cssBayan/index.html

https://commandor05-online-store.netlify.app/

https://rolling-scopes-school.github.io/evgueniazet-JSFE2022Q3/songbird/

https://rolling-scopes-school.github.io/evgueniazet-JSFE2023Q1/rs-css/

CONTACTS

email: zelenkoea19@gmail.com

phone: +375 25 538 43 25, +48 511 250 189 **github:** https://github.com/evgueniazet